[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Do you remember that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Oops.", "answer_tokens": ["Oops", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Steak sandwiches?", "question_tokens": ["Steak", "sandwiches", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Monica"]}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "And why not?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Because I'm in love with Monica.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "in", "love", "with", "Monica", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 85, "question": "You'd kissed everyone else?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "kissed", "everyone", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Everyone who ever walked on the set, I think --", "answer_tokens": ["Everyone", "who", "ever", "walked", "on", "the", "set", ",", "I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you watch?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "No, no, not much.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "not", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Why did I suck so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "I", "suck", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Yes, that's the neurosis.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "neurosis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Yes, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Would you want to change that or?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "want", "to", "change", "that", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "You would have kept going or you would have stopped?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "have", "kept", "going", "or", "you", "would", "have", "stopped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Oh, I would keep going.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "would", "keep", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "But why not have fun until they do?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "not", "have", "fun", "until", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yes, I guess the ideology was that like we would decide if that would be better.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "guess", "the", "ideology", "was", "that", "like", "we", "would", "decide", "if", "that", "would", "be", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", ":", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 203, "question": "You actually checked him, like really?", "question_tokens": ["You", "actually", "checked", "him", ",", "like", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I'm not used to -- yes --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "used", "to", "--", "yes", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Hilarious?", "question_tokens": ["Hilarious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "-- was it hilarious I was supposed to say--", "answer_tokens": ["--", "was", "it", "hilarious", "I", "was", "supposed", "to", "say", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "And -- yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 244, "question": "All you need to what?", "question_tokens": ["All", "you", "need", "to", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "All you need to succeed --", "answer_tokens": ["All", "you", "need", "to", "succeed", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "VB", "VBG", ",", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "It is?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "-- to be appealing, to --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "to", "be", "appealing", ",", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Oh, yes?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "On the show.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "the", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "I thought you were going back?", "question_tokens": ["I", "thought", "you", "were", "going", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I love you so much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "you", "so", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Who?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Me.", "answer_tokens": ["Me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "You know, did you notice that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "did", "you", "notice", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Maybe you haven't done it yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "you", "have", "n't", "done", "it", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "That I'm not there?", "question_tokens": ["That", "I", "'m", "not", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "It's called how well do you know your own project?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "called", "how", "well", "do", "you", "know", "your", "own", "project", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$900"]}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "$", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 346, "question": "-- what we were making before?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "we", "were", "making", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, $900 --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "$", "900", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "How -- how is everything going over there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "--", "how", "is", "everything", "going", "over", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "They're both fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "both", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "-- get to be on?", "question_tokens": ["--", "get", "to", "be", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "-- thing?", "question_tokens": ["--", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "-- that's exactly what the tag line is here.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "the", "tag", "line", "is", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Is that what you mean?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "-- interesting secrets that you've -- that you found out?", "question_tokens": ["--", "interesting", "secrets", "that", "you", "'ve", "--", "that", "you", "found", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "UDROW: We have -- like I am not allowed to give too much away.", "answer_tokens": ["UDROW", ":", "We", "have", "--", "like", "I", "am", "not", "allowed", "to", "give", "too", "much", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Do you fake them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fake", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "``", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Do you like being behind the scenes or in front?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "behind", "the", "scenes", "or", "in", "front", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I like it for \"Who Do You Think You Are?\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "it", "for", "``", "Who", "Do", "You", "Think", "You", "Are", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Which is just a -- it's -- those are just the words, the first letters for How Well Do You Know Your Own Project?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "just", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "--", "those", "are", "just", "the", "words", ",", "the", "first", "letters", "for", "How", "Well", "Do", "You", "Know", "Your", "Own", "Project", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "-- I'm going to sign a copy of one of your DVDs for you and give it back to you.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "sign", "a", "copy", "of", "one", "of", "your", "DVDs", "for", "you", "and", "give", "it", "back", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Isn't that great?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "great", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, that would be worth a lot, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "would", "be", "worth", "a", "lot", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What was the most successful one that got the most viewers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "most", "successful", "one", "that", "got", "the", "most", "viewers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I know that answer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "that", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I mean I knew that answer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "knew", "that", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Your most successful, OK?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "most", "successful", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Do you think Meryl Streep is more proud of her performance in \"Web Therapy\" or \"Sophie's Choice\"?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "Meryl", "Streep", "is", "more", "proud", "of", "her", "performance", "in", "``", "Web", "Therapy", "''", "or", "``", "Sophie", "'s", "Choice", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Oh, \"Web Therapy.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "``", "Web", "Therapy", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meryl Streep"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "And plus, that movie, I didn't see that movie, but is that whole movie just her going -- that one?", "question_tokens": ["And", "plus", ",", "that", "movie", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "see", "that", "movie", ",", "but", "is", "that", "whole", "movie", "just", "her", "going", "--", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "It's -- so there's other stuff in that?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "so", "there", "'s", "other", "stuff", "in", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "There's a lot of other difficult stuff in it.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "other", "difficult", "stuff", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you know the name of the -- of the title of that episode, what that episode was called?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "name", "of", "the", "--", "of", "the", "title", "of", "that", "episode", ",", "what", "that", "episode", "was", "called", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Oh, wow!", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "wow", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 530, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I don't know the --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "That's right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "So what's going on just with the body and the mind of an alcoholic?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "just", "with", "the", "body", "and", "the", "mind", "of", "an", "alcoholic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "ACK: Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["ACK", ":", "Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Corey"]}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "What could -- what could have been done?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "--", "what", "could", "have", "been", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "ACK: Well, you know, Corey had been in treatment before.", "answer_tokens": ["ACK", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Corey", "had", "been", "in", "treatment", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 662, "question": "So this is for primarily -- it's for first time, non- violent drug offenders, correct?", "question_tokens": ["So", "this", "is", "for", "primarily", "--", "it", "'s", "for", "first", "time", ",", "non-", "violent", "drug", "offenders", ",", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Yes, well --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "-- but that's who it -- that's who it's for, primarily, right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "but", "that", "'s", "who", "it", "--", "that", "'s", "who", "it", "'s", "for", ",", "primarily", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Actually, it's -- it's for who are really pretty seriously engaged in the criminal justice system.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "for", "who", "are", "really", "pretty", "seriously", "engaged", "in", "the", "criminal", "justice", "system", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["75 percent"]}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "And what is the success rate of drug court?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "is", "the", "success", "rate", "of", "drug", "court", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Well, 75 percent of our graduates never see another pair of handcuffs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "75", "percent", "of", "our", "graduates", "never", "see", "another", "pair", "of", "handcuffs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "How did you get from there to now here, sitting here on CNN?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "from", "there", "to", "now", "here", ",", "sitting", "here", "on", "CNN", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "TO", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Well, it's a long story.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "long", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "What do you think those guys should do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "those", "guys", "should", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "I would say seek treatment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "seek", "treatment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "So -- but there is a little window that opens for people, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "--", "but", "there", "is", "a", "little", "window", "that", "opens", "for", "people", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Who's not on the drug court side and what is their argument?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "not", "on", "the", "drug", "court", "side", "and", "what", "is", "their", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "Well, there really are one of two camps.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "really", "are", "one", "of", "two", "camps", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["past 24 years"]}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "How many people have we saved?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "have", "we", "saved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Well, in the past 24 years, we've saved a million people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "the", "past", "24", "years", ",", "we", "'ve", "saved", "a", "million", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 837, "question": "So, you now are a New York best-selling author, \"New York Times\" best selling author, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "now", "are", "a", "New", "York", "best-selling", "author", ",", "``", "New", "York", "Times", "''", "best", "selling", "author", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 838, "answer": "That is right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "VB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Do you like that better?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "that", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "You know, every job is it's own animal, I guess, and you just sort of have to learn the world and the world of \"Gilmore Girls\" was musical and precise, and the world of \"Parenthood\" is more about a family and they want it to sound messy and overlap and they shot it in a way that we can do that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "every", "job", "is", "it", "'s", "own", "animal", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "and", "you", "just", "sort", "of", "have", "to", "learn", "the", "world", "and", "the", "world", "of", "``", "Gilmore", "Girls", "''", "was", "musical", "and", "precise", ",", "and", "the", "world", "of", "``", "Parenthood", "''", "is", "more", "about", "a", "family", "and", "they", "want", "it", "to", "sound", "messy", "and", "overlap", "and", "they", "shot", "it", "in", "a", "way", "that", "we", "can", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Do you want to play a game?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "want", "to", "play", "a", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 882, "question": "It's called, how well do you know your own project, OK?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "called", ",", "how", "well", "do", "you", "know", "your", "own", "project", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 883, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 889, "question": "What's the first word?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "first", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 890, "answer": "Begin.", "answer_tokens": ["Begin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "Yes -- no, it gives me the willies.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--", "no", ",", "it", "gives", "me", "the", "willies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "Fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["Fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130726pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "What do you win?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "Your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]